I've held on for as long as I can
For the ones that I had to defend
I've been strong every day of my life
If she wants, death could take me this time
This world is a wasteland where nothing can grow
I used to have strength, but I ran out of hope
I know it's my fault that I'm here all alone
This world is a wasteland
Please let me go, go, go, go, go, go, go
If I could just lay my head down and rest
If there was nothing to fight or protect
Maybe then I could finally be free
Maybe death is like falling asleep
This world is a wasteland where nothing can grow
I used to have strength, but I ran out of hope
I know it's my fault that I'm here all alone
This world is a wasteland
I'm not ready to face it
Don't go saying goodbye
There's a beauty in changes
And I wanna try
This world is a wasteland where nothing can grow
If it weren't for you, I'd be here all alone
I know in my heart this is where we belong
This world is a wasteland
Don't let me go, go, go, go, go, go, go
Don't let me go